{"data":[{"question":"Nick is looking for another job because he feels that all that he has done never ___ his boss.","a":"satisfy","b":"serve","c":"support","d":"promise","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Satisfy: to make someone feel pleased by doing what they want","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"We didn't plan our book exhibition like that but it ___ well.","a":"tried out","b":"went on","c":"carried on","d":"worked out","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Work out:  if a problem or complicated situation works out, it gradually gets better or gets solved","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"The group of tourists ___ the train until it disappeared into the distance.","a":"watched","b":"saw","c":"observed","d":"noticed","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Watch:   to look at someone or something for a period of time, paying attention to what is happening","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"___ that model and then try to copy what he does.","a":"Glance at","b":"Mind","c":"Watch","d":"Stare at","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Watch: to pay attention to a situation that interests or worries you to see how it develops","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"Do you think the Lakers will be beaten? \"Um","a":"prefer","b":"hope","c":"want","d":"expect","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Hope: to want something to happen or be true and to believe that it is possible or likely","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"It's a wonderful project. But who's going to ___ it ___? \"I think Gloria and Wilson will.\"","a":"carry, out","b":"set, aside","c":"get, through","d":"take, in","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Carry out: to do something that you have said you will do or that someone has asked you to do","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"The conference ___ last weekend.","a":"was happened","b":"was taken place","c":"took place","d":"broke out","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Take place: to happen, especially after being planned or arranged","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"These kinds of raincoats ___ well.","a":"are not sold","b":"don't sell","c":"were not sold","d":"won't be sold","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Simple present tense+ active voice","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"The library ___ at 9:00 p.m. on workdays.","a":"is closed","b":"closes","c":"will be closed","d":"is closing","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Simple present tense (Use the Simple Present to express the idea that an action is repeated or usual. The action can be a habit, a hobby, a daily event, a scheduled event or something that often happens)+ active voice","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"While this tough meat is being cooked, more water would ___ it.","a":"add to","b":"be added to","c":"be added up to","d":"be adding to","answer":"2","explain":"That's right! You chose the correct response.","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"}]}